A Guide to the Gravely Family Papers, 1753-1988
Library of Virginia
- Series V: Subject files
  - Tobacco stencils--Choice Extra Fine Pounds, Leatherwood, Va. (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Tobacco stencils--Golden Henry Co. Pounds, D. J. Walsh & Company (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Tobacco stencils--Peyton Gravely/P. B. Gravely (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Tobacco stencils--J. W. Gravely's Double Eagle; B. F. Gravely Leatherwood, Va.; Natural Leaf; B. F. Gravely Superior Pounds; Star of Henry (R. J. Reynolds) (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Treasury Department, United States (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Tredegar Company and Baldwin & Wight (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Typwriters (Arrow Electric Company; Hammond Typewriters; list of items) (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Union Republican Party of Virginia Convention, 1867 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - United Service (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - University of Virginia, Class of 1935 reunion, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Virginia State Horticultural Society (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - W. O. Minter, Dealer in General Merchandise (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - W. W. Waddill Real Estate (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Warrock-Richardson Almanac, 1883, presented by B. F. Gravely & Sons (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - Western United Gas and Electric Company (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - Woman's Missionary Society Report Form (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - Yearbooks, Garden Club of Martinsville (Va.), 1927 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - Yearbooks, DAR, Patrick Henry Chapter, 1917-1936 (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - Yearbooks, Woman's Club, 1929-1933 (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - Miscellaneous papers (Box 45, Folder 37)
- Series VI: Legal documents
  - B.F. Gravely & Sons vs. B.F. Gravely & Sons, 1888 (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - Bonds and banknotes, includes CSA, 1799-1869 (Box 45, Folder 39)
  - Contracts, 1906-1917 (Box 45, Folder 40)
  - Deeds, plats, patents, 1759-1894 (Box 45, Folder 41)
  - Deeds, 1891-1973 (Box 45, Folder 42)
  - Deeds, plats, surveys, 1873-1902 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Estate papers, Jones, Thomas, 1857-1859 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Estate papers, Richardson, Elijah, 1853-1879 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Estate papers (Inventory, Sale) 1859 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Estate papers, 1813-1879 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Plats, Estate of C.Y. Thomas, 1949-1966 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Powers of attorney, 1851-1865 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Receipts, 1865-1934 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Suit papers, 1852-1899 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Wills, 1837-1879 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Wills, 1893-1921 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Will, Hairston Ann M., 1906 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- Series VII: Miscellaneous
  - Calling cards (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Holiday cards (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Invitations, announcements, programs (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Invitations, announcements, programs (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Invitations, announcements, programs (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Invitations, announcements, programs (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Invitations, announcements, programs (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Collegiate publications, 1874-1905 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Ornate letterheads (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Ornate letterheads (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Series VIII: Transcripts
  - Gravely, B.F., Correspondence, 1781-1866 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Gravely, B.F., Correspondence, 1861-1865 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Gravely, Peyton, Correspondence, 1824-1867 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Gravely, Peyton, Papers, 1825-1847 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Mullins, S.J., Diary, 1857-1865 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Thomas, C.Y., Correspondence, 1804-1861 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Thomas, C.Y, Correspondence, 1862-1863 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Thomas, C.Y., Correspondence, 1864-1865 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Thomas, C.Y., Correspondence, 1865-1867 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Thomas, C.Y., Correspondence, 1867-1874 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Thomas, C.Y., Correspondence, 1875-1878 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Ships log, "Omega", 1849-1853 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Series IX: Business records
  - Subseries 1: General
    - Fernald, W.L., 1870-1885 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Fernald, W.L., 1877-1885 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Fernald, W.L., 1881 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Fernald, W.L., 1882 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Fernald, W.L., Mrs., 1881-1886 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Fernald family, 1859-1902 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Fernald family, 1873 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Fernald family, 1874 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Fernald family, 1875 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Fernald family, 1876 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Fernald family, 1877 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Fernald family, 1878 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Fernald family, 1879 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Fernald family, 1880 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Fernald family, 1883 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Fernald family, 1884 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Fernald family, 1885 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Fernald family, 1886 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Fernald family, 1890-1901 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Fernald family, nd (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1879-1884 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1885-1889 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1885-1889 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1890-1894 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1890-1894 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1895-1899 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1895-1899 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1895-1899 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1895-1899 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1895-1899 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1895-1899 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1900-1904 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1900-1904 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1900-1904 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1900-1904 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1900-1904 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1900-1904 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1900-1904 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1900-1904 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1900-1904 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1900-1904 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1900-1904 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1900-1904 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1900-1904 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1900-1904 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1905-1909 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1905-1909 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1905-1909 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1905-1909 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1910-1914 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1910-1914 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1910-1914 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1910-1914 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1910-1914 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1910-1914 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1910-1914 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1915-1919 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1915-1919 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1915-1919 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1915-1919 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1920-1924 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1920-1924 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1920-1924 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1925-1929 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1925-1929 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1925-1929 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1925-1929 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1925-1929 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1925-1929 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1925-1929 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1925-1929 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1925-1929 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1930-1934 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Gravely, Harry C., 1930-1940 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Gravely, Harry C., nd (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Gravely, Harry C., nd (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Gravely, Hope Thomas, 1885-1889 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Gravely, Hope Thomas, 1890-1894 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Gravely, Hope Thomas, 1895-1899 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Gravely, Hope Thomas, 1900-1904 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Gravely, Hope Thomas, 1905-1909 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Gravely, Hope Thomas, 1910-1914 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Gravely, Hope Thomas, 1915-1919 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Gravely, Hope Thomas, 1920-1924 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Gravely, Hope Thomas, 1925-1929 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Gravely, Hope Thomas, 1930-1931 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Gravely, Hope Thomas, nd (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Business 1845-1881 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Notes, Bonds, 1862-1929 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Business records, 1836-1870 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts, 1838-1849 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts, 1838-1841 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts, 1838-1877 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, 1844-1871 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, 1842-1844 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, 1845-1847 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts, 1845-1850 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts, 1845-1858 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts, 1847-1861 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Hamlett's trustees receipts, 1840-1859 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Thomas and Flood, 1844-1870 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts, 1850-1854 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts, 1855-1859 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts, 1858-1870 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts, 1859 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts, 1860 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts, 1860-1861 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts, 1865-1869 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts, 1869 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts, 1870-1879 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts 1871 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts, 1870-1873 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts, 1872 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts, 1873 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts, 1873 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts, 1873-1874 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts, 1874 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts, 1875 (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts, 1866-1877 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts, 1876 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts, 1851-1909 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts, 1861-1911 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts, 1866-1871 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts, 1870-1884 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipts, Accounts, 1877-1881 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Receipt book, 1852-1857 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Bonds, Receipts 1830-1861 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Bonds, Receipts, 1854-1860 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Bonds, Receipts, 1861-1862 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Bonds, Receipts, 1863-1864 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Bonds, Receipts, 1865-1872 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Bills of sale, 1855-1866 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Legal papers, 1840-1923 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Fees to court clerks, 1846-1860 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Officials receipts, 1845-1862 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Treasurer of Henry County (Va.), 1871-1875 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Thomas, C.Y., James D. Davidson, 1852-1860 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Methodist Church, 1856 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Heirs of William Davis, 1857-1860 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Confederate salt receipts, 1862-1863 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Estate Inc., Bylaws, 1953-1960 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Estate Inc., Charter, 1961 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Estate Inc., City Park, 1939-1888 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Estate Inc., Contracts with city, 1955 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Estate Inc., Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Estate Inc., Thomas land 1957-1964 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Estate Inc., Deeds, 1953-1966 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Estate Inc., Deeds, 1959-1969 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Estate Inc., Presbyterian Church, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Estate Inc., Rights of way, 1950-1960 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Thomas, C.Y., Estate Inc., Tax forms, 1961 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Thomas, Frank 1885-1886 (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Thomas family, 1838-1870 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Subseries 2: Individuals
    - Austin, Charles F., 1864 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Carter, Tom, 1868 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Clay, J.H., 1882 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Davis, W.O., 1904 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Gravely, Benjamin F., 1854-1964 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Gravely, C.B., County levy receipt, 1867 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Gravely, C.B., Deputy collector, 1875-1879 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Gravely, George C., nd (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Gravely, Harold, 1954-1959 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Gravely, George D., 1848-1865 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Gravely J.T., Correspondence, 1877-1903 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Gravely, J.T., Invoices, 1893-1894 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Gravely, Jabez, 1849-1865 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Gravely, Jabez, Sr., 1849-1865 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Gravely, Joseph, 1850 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Gravely, Julia C., 1899 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Gravely, N.W., 1904-1930 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Gravely, Nannie, 1902 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Gravely, Paul, 1912-1964 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Gravely, Peyton, 1846-1852 (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Gravely, R.P. and B.F., 1902 (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - Gravely, R.P., 1904-1914 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Gravely, Willis, 1866-1867 (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - Gravely family, 1818-1870 (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - Gravely family, 1890-1958 (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - Grigg, W.W., 1856 (Box 61, Folder 26)
    - Jennings, S.B., nd (Box 61, Folder 27)
    - Lagenly, J.A., 1876 (Box 61, Folder 28)
    - Lawrence, Darling, 1871 (Box 61, Folder 29)
    - Lawrence, William, 1902 (Box 61, Folder 30)
    - Lewis, J.P. 1890 (Box 61, Folder 31)
    - McCaull, P.H., 1890-1891 (Box 61, Folder 32)
    - Minter, Silas, 1853-1868 (Box 61, Folder 33)
    - Minter, William S., 1864-1867 (Box 61, Folder 34)
    - Mullins, H.G., 1850-1898 (Box 61, Folder 35)
    - Pedigo, L.G., 1902 (Box 61, Folder 36)
    - Reamey, H.D., 1900 (Box 61, Folder 37)
    - Reamey, H.D. Mrs., 1895 (Box 61, Folder 38)
    - Reammey, W.D. & H.D., 1896 (Box 61, Folder 39)
    - Sheffield, Bettie, 1880-1881 (Box 61, Folder 40)
    - Sheffield, W.A., Col., 1848-1878 (Box 61, Folder 41)
    - Sheffield, William A., 1848-1874 (Box 61, Folder 42)
    - Thomas, L.S., 1880-1882 (Box 61, Folder 43)
    - Thomas, L.S., 1889 (Box 61, Folder 44)
    - Thomas, L.S., 1890-1894 (Box 61, Folder 45)
    - Thomas, L.S., 1903-1925 (Box 61, Folder 46)
    - Thomas, Matilda, 1886-1902 (Box 61, Folder 47)
    - Thomas, Nancy, 1847-1964 (Box 61, Folder 48)
    - Watkins, James W., 1835-1844 (Box 61, Folder 49)
    - Wells, Mathew C., 1869 (Box 61, Folder 50)
    - Wingfield, William H., 1868-1870 (Box 61, Folder 51)
    - Wiyett, Robert, 1897-1902 (Box 61, Folder 52)
    - Wyatt, Harrison, 1843-1847 (Box 61, Folder 53)
    - Unidentified, 1869 (Box 61, Folder 54)
    - Unidentified, 1860-1902 (Box 61, Folder 55)
    - Unidentified, 1864-1868 (Box 61, Folder 56)
    - Unidentified, 1877-1926 (Box 61, Folder 57)
    - Unidentified, 1858-1893 (Box 61, Folder 58)
    - Unidentified, 1875-1927 (Box 61, Folder 59)
    - Unidentified, 1866-1925 (Box 61, Folder 60)
    - Unidentified, 1857-1909 (Box 61, Folder 61)
    - Unidentified, 1850-1881 (Box 61, Folder 62)
  - Subseries 3: Correspondence
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1843-1845 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1846 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1847 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1848 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1849 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1850 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1851 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1852 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1853 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1854 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1855 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1856 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1857 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1858 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1859 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1860 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1861 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1862-1864 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1865 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1866 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1867 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1867 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1868 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1868 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1869 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1869 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1870 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1871 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1872-1879 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1880 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1881 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co. trademark registration, 1881 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1882 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1883 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1886 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1890-1894 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1892 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1892-1893 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1895-1899 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1895-1899 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1895-1899 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1895-1899 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1895-1899 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1895-1899 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1895-1899 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1895-1899 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1895-1899 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1895-1899 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1895-1899 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1895-1899 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1900-1904 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1900-1904 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1900-1904 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1900-1904 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1900-1904 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1900-1904 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1900-1904 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1900-1904 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1900-1904 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1900-1904 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1900-1904 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1900-1904 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1900-1904 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1900-1904 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1900-1904 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1900-1904 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1900-1904 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1905-1909 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1905-1909 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1905-1909 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1910-1914 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1910-1914 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1915-1919 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1926-1929 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1935-1939 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., nd (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 4: Receipts, Accounts
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1840 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1843 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1845 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1845-1855 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1846 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1846 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1846 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1847 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1848 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1849 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1850 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1851 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1852 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1852 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1853 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1854 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1855 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1856 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1857 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1858 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1859 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1860 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1861 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1861 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1862 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1863 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1864 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1865 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1866 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1866 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1866 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1867 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1867 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1867 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1868 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1868 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1869 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1870 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1870 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1871 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1872 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1872 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1874 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1875 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1876 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1877 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1878 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - B.F. Gravely and Co., 1879 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Subseries 5: Invoices and bills
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1880 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1880 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1880 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1881 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1881 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1881 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1881 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1881 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1881 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1882 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1882 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1882 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1882 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1882-1883 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1884 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1885-1887 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1888 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - B.F. Gravely and Sons, 1888 (Box 73, Folder 11)